Green Dolphin Street Prison.
Nicknamed "The Aquarium".
In its time,
it gave birth
to mystery and power.
A power invisible
to ordinary men.
A power and a mystery
steeped in filth.
Jolyne was sentenced
to five additional years in a punitive
ward for her escape attempt.
It will all begin after her release.
All of it.
Before that,
I must look into something.
It concerns another inmate.
Her name is...
Hermes Costello.
Jolyne has already met her.
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm talking to you, scum!
The infirmary?
How did I end up here?
Shit.
It's the guy who cleans the toilets.
I worked my ass off for that money.
Goddamn it!
Oh, I remember now.
I cut myself
in the palm of my right hand.
I had a fever, too.
But my hand
is almost fully healed.
Was I dreaming?
Wait.
It's all coming back to me.
Just before I arrived here
to serve my five-year sentence
for my robbery,
I found an amulet.
It was in the laundry room
of the holding prison.
I cut myself on it,
it pissed me off and I sold it to...
What was her name again?
Oh, right, Gwess.
Anyway, I sold her the amulet.
And that night...
something made me pass out.
Since then, I've been here.
Have I been bedridden this whole time?
My hand feels better.
What the...
I just peeled
that sticker off my hand.
Is my memory playing tricks on me?
The year 1492.
Christopher Columbus discovers America.
Bugs Bunny's birthday
is July 27th.
No, my memory works fine.
What the...
I'm sure I already peeled it off.
Hold on, what? My shoes...
There are...
one, two...
three, four, five, six...
Ow!
There are five? They merged!
Is the heat making me lose it?
And what about the sticker?
That's the one I threw away...
No way...
That's gross!
– You're making a racket!
– Keep it down, will you?
It's nothing. Go back to sleep.
Damn it.
No.
The heat has nothing to do with it.
I'm holding this shoe,
I can feel its weight.
The sticker...
when I attach it to an object,
that object gets duplicated.
When I remove it,
something gets destroyed
and the original object is restored.
This sticker...
I know it sounds crazy,
but there's no doubt about it.
It came out of my hand!
Well,
now that I've accepted it,
it's actually really useful.
This is amazing.
No need to strain my brain.
The sticker comes out of my hand.
It's reality.
You bastard.
Give me back my money.
What...
It's gone.
He didn't notice a thing.
I grabbed it without thinking.
This disc...
What does it do?
Your temperature is normal.
You can go back to your cell.
Wait, I have a question.
The guy who cleans the toilets,
is he a model prisoner? What...
And what would you do with that information?
Next!
The inmate who does the cleaning?
How would I know?
No idea.
It's not a CD,
but it has the same shape
and it reflects light
the same way.
But it's soft and elastic.
And then
I saw another disc on his face.
There were two things like that
on his face.
What is this?
It's projecting something.
The money I took
from the sick inmates.
It's mine.
Five thousand dollars.
No one will ever find it here.
This image...
McQueen.
Would you cooperate with me,
as my associate?
McQueen!
What did I just see?
It was like I was looking
into someone else's memory!
I heard...
you've been asking questions about me.
I've stalked people before,
but I've never been stalked
by a woman before.
Yeah, that's a first.
Who the hell are you?
I saw
discs coming out of your face!
Discs?
I don't remember anything. What discs?
I'm such a loser!
I don't remember anything!
Why are you yelling all of a sudden?
You stole my money at the infirmary.
This very morning!
Money? Now that you mention it.
I had a huge amount of money,
which I hid somewhere.
But...
I forgot where!
Hey, are you feeling okay?
Are you screwing with me?
You asked me
if I was feeling okay?
How sweet of you!
It's been so long
since I last talked with a woman!
No, actually it's the first time.
I've never had
a sincere conversation with a woman before.
I'm over the moon.
I hope someday I can live
with a wonderful woman like you.
But that will never happen.
I'm pathetic, aren't I?
Yes, I'm a piece of trash.
I want to die.
What...
What the hell are you doing?
What is that thing?
That thing!
McQueen...
pure evil resides within you.
You mean no harm to anyone.
You believe you're not a burden to others.
You see yourself as a victim,
and you never give anything back,
yet you always hope
that someone will save you.
That is precisely why
you are the worst.
You drag others down with you.
You are the purest form of evil.
I really love you, McQueen.
If you ever came across my enemies
inside the walls of this prison,
I'm sure you would clean them out
and take care of them.
Damn it! When he hangs himself,
I end up hanged too!
Help!
Somebody!
I'm fading.
If his body was lowered,
would I be able to breathe?
Sticker.
He has strange powers, just like me.
So I'm not the only one!
Oh my God.
Who the hell are you?
Why did you hang yourself?
You saved me?
I owe you my life.
Who the hell are you?
What do you want from me?
I know you have a power!
A power?
I don't know what you're talking about.
But rest assured,
I won't do it again.
I see things clearly now.
I'm in your debt,
you saved my life.
Someday, I'll return the favor.
No need, don't worry.
It was nothing.
What the hell are you doing?
What is that?
Those scars...
He's suicidal!
He isn't even aware of his power.
This sucks.
I'm even
in the same position as him.
Damn it, he's so far away from me.
You big bastard!
Damn it!
The disc!
I don't understand anything
of what's going on,
but it must have something
to do with these discs!
Let me die.
I promised you
I'd return the favor,
but a guy like me
will never be able to do that,
because I'm a piece of shit!
I want nothing to do with you!
Get away from me, or I'll kill you!
Yes, please!
I wouldn't mind being killed
by a beautiful woman like you!
It seems she picked up a disc
in the toilets.
I don't know why,
but I think it belonged to me.
I wonder if she'll give it back to me.
No, probably not.
Let me through!
I have a pass.
I'm heading back to the women's prison.
Goddamn son of a...!
I have to stay as far away
as possible from that lunatic.
I need to get back
to my cell.
I knew it.
Your power has awakened.
Know that this power of yours
is called a Stand.
Stands attract one another
as if they gravitated
around one another.
Without any logic.
That's why you ran into
that janitor.
A kid, here?
You picked up and sold
Jolyne's amulet.
That's why she asked me
to protect you.
You know Jolyne?
What happened to her?
Our enemy has the ability
to steal souls.
We're looking for a soul he stole.
Stolen?
His name is Whitesnake.
If you know anything,
please tell me.
A soul?
You wouldn't be talking
about that disc, by any chance?
That disc!
It belonged to the janitor.
What's so important about these discs?
Did he have two of them?
Two discs? That's right.
A memory disc and a Stand disc.
The discs work in pairs.
Two discs make up a soul.
If we could get the other disc,
we could learn more
about Whitesnake!
Hell, no.
Not this!
He's still following me.
Damn it! I thought I'd gotten far enough away.
What's going on?
Electricity! That bastard!
He's electrocuting himself!
It stopped.
It's the resistance.
A man doesn't die
from a measly 100 volts.
Our bodies have resistance.
That's why it stopped.
His suicide attempt failed.
But...
if he wants to try
electrocuting himself again,
he must be out looking
for a saline solution right now.
A saline solution doubles conductivity
and therefore lowers resistance.
The electric current will pass through the heart,
burning the organ!
A saline solution, huh?
It's used in IV drips
and as a disinfectant.
There's plenty at the infirmary!
I can't go any farther.
There are too many inmates
near the stairs!
I'm gonna smash his face
and take the other disc from him.
No other choice!
Stop! Don't do it!
Look at my arm!
It's burned, just like yours.
You've gained a power.
Every one of your suicide attempts
shows up on me!
Stop trying to kill yourself.
Life can be pretty good.
Four years ago,
I was doing some cleaning.
I was inspecting my firearm
in my apartment.
But for some reason,
it was loaded.
It was an accident.
I live on the tenth floor.
Right as the shot went off,
a woman jumped out of a window.
It was like the lottery.
Some people win millions.
Sometimes, the opposite
happens.
She was supposed to die
by smashing her head on the ground.
Everyone believed
I had targeted and killed her from the 11th floor.
To the judge,
I was a "merciless killer".
That's me, damn it!
Wait!
Panties.
Has a woman
ever given you her panties?
Don't you think you'd be lucky
if a girl gave you her panties?
You're at rock bottom right now.
But imagine.
If a girl gives you her panties,
you become lucky
even when your life looks like crap.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
But you're going to get them.
I'm going to give you
the ones I'm wearing right now!
Give me your panties?
I keep my promises.
But remember this:
everybody hates Mondays.
We all wait for Saturday
to come so we can have fun.
It's not Monday every day!
I was arrested on a Saturday.
You're talking nonsense
to give me hope,
but I bet you're bluffing
to save your own skin.
Not at...
You're pretending to be nice
to get yourself out of this situation.
You don't believe a word
of what you're saying.
Am I wrong?
That's how
everyone treats me.
Nobody likes trash.
But I'm worse than trash.
Nobody looks at me.
That's my life!
Wait.
It's true,
I'm sweet-talking you because I don't want to die.
But listen to me.
Whitesnake is using you.
He's exploiting your weakness.
If you weren't trying to kill yourself,
none of this would have happened.
You're the one being selfish right now,
you bastard!
You really are a good person.
Wonderful.
Your words were sincere.
I'm lucky, that's for sure.
I stumbled by chance
upon such a beautiful woman.
Thank you!
If I can die with you...
If I can spend eternity with you,
then I am blessed!
He's a piece of trash.
He is, without a doubt,
rotten to the core!
I'm not alone!
– There we go!
– Let go of that switch, you bastard!
That was close.
Goddamn son of a...!
I managed to stick the sticker on him.
The electricity is burning it.
Once it's completely burned up,
the copy he made...
will be destroyed.
Holy freaking hell.
I remember now.
He hid the money he stole,
$5,000.
I'll be cashing in on that, you little shit.
And then there's Whitesnake.
He's the reason
I went through all that.
What are you up to, exactly?
I have to go see her. Jolyne...
Jolyne Kujo.